ACTWU's Vice-President's Office Records 5619/029
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New York Urban Coalition, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- June O'Grady, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Pay Board, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Citizen's Committee on Population and the American Future, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Public Affairs Committee [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Public Affairs Committee [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- United Nations, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Wednesday Club, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Esther Peterson, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Stanley Ruttenberg, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Imports. Four Unions, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  ACWA, ILGWU, TWUA, UTWU
- Imports. Public Relations, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Health Insurance [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Health Insurance [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation. Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation. Publicity. [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1972 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation. Publicity. [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Committee on Discussion and Debate: National University Extension Association, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation. Luncheon Meeting, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Sidney Hillman. National Portrait Gallery, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Election, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Howard D. Samuel. Personal, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- United Garment Workers, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Garment Center Task Force, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Howard D. Samuel. Speeches and Appearances, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Imports. Legislation, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Imports. Correspondence, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Imports. General, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Issues, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Imports. 807, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Imports. ACWA, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Manpower, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Carnegie [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Carnegie [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Howard D. Samuel. Personal, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Information Requests, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Special Mailings and Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Task Force, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Newsreporter, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  v.1:no.1 (1975:Apr.)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Memos, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Board of Directors, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  Correspondence
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Trade Union Fund Raising, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Finance, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Foundation Proposals, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Lobbying Efforts, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Pending, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Congressional Advisory Board, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Statistics, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. By-Laws, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Stationery (Box 8, Folder 28)
  Old and New
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Articles of Incorporation, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Statement of Purpose (Box 9, Folder 2)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. List of Board of Directors, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Minutes, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  October 18, 1974.
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Literature Distributed, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Literature, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Publicity [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Publicity [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Activities, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Publicity on Jobs, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Leon Keyserling, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Research Paper no.1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Speech Material, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Economists, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. List for Conference Invitations, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Conference Planning Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Conference Speeches and Transcript, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Conference Follow-Up Correspondence, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. National Federation of Settlement Houses, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Joint Economic Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  Full Employment
- AFL-CIO, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Congressional Preparations for Full Employment Bill, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Arkansas Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Baltimore Joint Board, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Boston Joint Board, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Insurance Fund, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Central States Joint Board, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Chicago Joint Board, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Chicago. United Dwellings Foundation of Metropolitan Chicago, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Chicago. Sidney Hillman Health Center, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Cincinnati Joint Board, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Cleaners and Dyers Joint Board, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Cleveland Joint Board, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Detroit and Midwestern States Joint Board, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Clothing Workers Joint Board, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Green Cards, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Election, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Farah. Names for Ad, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Farah. Names for Ad. Correspondence, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Farah. Howard D. Samuel, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- National Manpower Advisory Committee, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- National Manpower Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- National Manpower Advisory Committee, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- COPE (Committee on Political Education), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- COPE (Committee on Political Education), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- COPE (Committee on Political Education), 1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- COPE (Committee on Political Education), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- COPE (Committee on Political Education), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Farah. Strikers Fund, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Farah. Strikers Fund, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Catholic Center at New York University, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Farah. Support, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- New York Urban Coalition, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Day Care, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Immigration, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Staff Newsletter, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Imports [folder 1 of 3], 1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Imports [folder 2 of 3], 1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Imports [folder 3 of 3], 1972 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Imports [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Imports [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- APEC (Amalgamated Political Education Committee), 1972 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Aging, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Index to GEB Report, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Index cards
- Public Relations Subject Index (Box 12, Folder 2)
- National Committee for Full Employment. Full Employment Action Council. Board of Directors and Task Force Index (Box 12, Folder 3)